techforless.com 2008-12-17

# Refurbished Computers, Laptops, Monitors - Cheap Prices!

## Our Policy in Summary:

Your information is safe with us. We do not sell, rent or otherwise share your information with anyone. Tech for Less LLC is a member of the Better Business Bureau (BBB) and has the earned the Online Reliability Seal. |   
---|---  

### What Personally Identifiable Information Is Collected When Making a Purchase?

When you make a purchase on our site, you provide the following information:  
\- Name   
\- E-mail address   
\- Billing and shipping address   
\- Telephone number   
\- Credit card number and expiration date, or other form of payment   
  
### Data Security:

Tech for Less LLC uses a secured network to handle your personal information. A secured server is used and information is transmitted via SSL encryption. This security technology makes it safe to enter and transmit your credit card over the Internet by providing the following protections: |   
---|---  
Server authentication - keeps out imposters  
Privacy using encryption - keeps out eavesdroppers  
Data integrity - keeps out vandals   
  
### Personal Information:

Personal information relating to you and your order history are only available to employees of Tech for Less LLC and cannot be modified by web visitors. We do not store your information nor your credit card number on our Web Site. 

### Navigational Information:

TechForLess.com logs the user's Internet Protocol Address (IP). An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your PC every time you browse the Internet and it does not contain any personal information. Information from IP addresses is used for system administration, to examine overall traffic trends, troubleshooting, etc. This information is used only in the aggregate form. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information, unless you make a purchase. When you make a purchase the IP address is logged with the order, but is not shared with any other companies or agencies except in the case of credit card fraud where information is provided to the appropriate authorities. 

### Cookies:

A cookie is a small piece of information that web sites use to remember information about users. Tech for Less LLC uses session cookies to provide continuity from page to page. Within a single visit, these cookies store information such as your shopping list to simplify checkout. They do not contain any personally identifying information. You can disable your cookies at any time through your browser options. We do not use cookies to establish profiles of users to our site. 

### Transactional Information:

When you make a purchase from TechForLess.com we will ask for information such as name, address and credit card information. This information is stored in a secured database, only accessible to employees with access rights to this information. User's credit information is transferred over a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) line. This ensures your information is encrypted and cannot be read by any other Internet users. The secure mode begins upon ordering. Tech for Less will not charge your credit card until your order is shipped. 

To be sure you're browsing secure pages, check your Web browser's status bar (located at the bottom of the window) for the closed padlock icon. This icon appears in the latest versions of Internet Explorer and Netscape Navigator to tell you that you are viewing a secure web page. Also, all browsers display an "s" after the "http" (https://...) in the Web site address to indicate that you're in a secure environment. 

We also protect your purchase by preventing the shipment of merchandise to a fraudulent address. All billing addresses are verified electronically and all alternate shipping addresses are verified manually. Any customer shipping to an address that differs from the billing address must put this alternate address on file with his or her credit card company. We then call the credit card issuer to verify that the customer has indeed put the information on file. 

### Managing your account:

Personal information relating to you and your order history are only available to authorized Tech for Less LLC employees. You cannot edit this information online. 

### Opt-out:

Tech for Less LLC will give visitors a choice whether they wish to be on the mailing list, receive promotions, information or updates about the site. The visitor may choose to remove their name from the site's mailing list by clicking the "remove" link at the bottom of any promotional email communication. 

We work with FetchBack to display Retargeted ads to our site prospects, on our behalf, across the Internet. They collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to our Website, and your interaction with our products and services. The anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. No Personally Identifiable Information is collected during in this process. To read FetchBack’s Privacy Policy, click [here](http://www.fetchback.com/privacy.html). If you do not want FetchBack to collect this information, you may opt out of their service. Opting out will not in any way effect your use of our site. To Opt-Out of FetchBack Retargeting, please click [here](http://www.fetchback.com/optout.html).

### Data Sharing:

Tech for Less LLC does not provide any third party with any individually identifiable information other than that which is necessary to complete your order. Specifically, Tech for Less LLC gives your name, shipping address, phone number, and order information to our shipping carrier. Tech for Less LLC also supplies your name, billing address, and credit card information to the credit card processor who bills your account. Tech for Less LLC has strict guidelines requiring all third parties to keep any shared personal information confidential. 

### Outside Links:

TechForLess.com may direct you to other sites with which we associate or are outside our service. These other sites may use their own "cookies", collect data or solicit personal information from you. Please be advised TechForLess.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and guidelines on these sites. TechForLess.com suggests you review their policies before you utilize their site. 

## Customer Service Policy

### Policy Regarding Credit Card Fraud:

Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. 

With Visa's Zero Liability policy*, your liability for unauthorized transactions is $0-you pay nothing! *Certain restrictions, limitations and exclusions apply. American Express also has an Online Fraud Protection Guarantee. Discover has 100% Fraud Protection. 

### Confirmation, Pricing and Availability Information:

Tech for Less LLC makes every effort to get your order to you as soon as possible. All advertised products are in stock. When you place your order before 4:00 pm M.S.T., we will ship your order the same business day. If there is a problem with your order you will receive an email providing more details about the problem within one business day. Special and Custom orders may take longer to process. 

### Payment information:

You may pay for your order with a Visa, MasterCard, Discover or American Express card. Orders may be made via our web site or by phone at 1-719-886-8000. If you prefer to make other payment arrangements, please contact our Sales Department at the number shown above. 

### Shipping Rates and Policies:

Tech for Less LLC charges based on the weight and dimensions of the item. Add items to your shopping cart and then enter your zip code and click update. You will see your actual shipping charges. Shipments to Alaska and Hawaii may only be shipped by 2nd day or Next Day Air service. All orders are shipped using UPS, FedEx or other appropriate freight carrier. Tech for Less will ship products billed to our customers shipping account also. Delivery time varies depending on the service level selected. 

### Contact Information:

Tech for Less LLC  
1610 Garden of the Gods Rd., Suite 100  
Colorado Springs, CO 80907

M-F 8:00am to 6:00pm MST

| 

Local Phone: 1-719-886-8000  
Fax: 1-719-886-8001 

E-mail: [sales@techforless.com](mailto:sales@techforless.com)  
  
---|---  
**Tech for Less LLC**  
---  
Outlet Store Location: |     | Toll Free: 1-866-880-1230  
1610 Garden of the Gods Rd. |     | Local Phone: 1-719-886-8000  
Colorado Springs, CO 80907 |     | Fax: 1-719-886-8001  
   
M-F 7:30am to 6:30pm MST |     | Sales/Product Questions: [sales@techforless.com](mailto:sales@techforless.com)  
Sat 9:00am to 4:00pm MST |     | After Sales Support: [customerservice@techforless.com](mailto:customerservice@techforless.com)  
Sun 11:00am to 4:00pm MST |     |
